I've thought of a way
to protect myself
and protect her.
Her?
Bai Weng,
Fenghuang Police Station is hiring.
Pull some strings
and sign me up.
You want to be a police officer?
I must find out why
our brothers went missing.
And
my father's death.
The boss said back then
that you are not allowed to seek revenge.
Being a police officer makes it easier to act.
Besides,
I can carry a gun justifiably.
Let me do it.
Otherwise, I won't be able to eat or sleep.
You're awake.
Peter, let me go.
Miss Jiang.
You brought this upon yourself.
You.
You saw it.
Stop.
Don't cry out loud.
I hate noise the most.
Otherwise, you'll end up like him.
Understand?
You actually used these boys and girls for experiments.
You are a heartless beast.
They were all homeless,
pitiful people.
Don't worry.
I let them eat their fill before they died.
You are different, Miss Jiang.
You have a perfect face
and a pair of perfect eyes.
Get lost, you filthy foreigner!
Senior Sister.
Stop hitting him.
If you keep hitting him, we won't get anything out of him.
Siyao.
Are you okay?
Don't be afraid. We are the police.
Don't be afraid.
You should be glad you didn't do anything.
Otherwise, I would have crippled you.
Peter,
we now have evidence proving
that you smuggled illegal drugs
and raped women.
Do you plead guilty?
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
What the hell is he saying?
What is he babbling about?
How am I supposed to record this?
Go
and call Ye Shian over.
He's not a police officer.
He can't interrogate suspects.
Let him be a temporary translator.
There are precedents for special cases, right?
You don't understand Chinese either.
Let me ask you.
That tattoo on your chest,
what does it mean?
Speak English.
If you don't explain it clearly,
do you think you can really leave?
Before the concession police arrive,
I won't say a word.
No one can protect you.
Try me.
I will be out soon.
Peter,
this is China.
China.
It is exactly because I am in China
that I can do whatever I want
without being punished.
Don't forget,
I am a citizen of the British Empire
and enjoy extraterritorial rights here.
Your country is backward and weak.
I will not be judged by Chinese law.
Why are you here?
English translation.
People from the British Concession Police Station are here.
They want to extradite Peter to the station.
That's enough.
Exactly.
You might be immune to Chinese law.
But as for this beating from a Chinese,
you have to take it.
What are you doing?
Police beating a foreign citizen will incur diplomatic consequences.
What a coincidence.
I am not a police officer.
I...
Hello, I am the inspector of the Phoenix Police Department,
Jiang Siyao.
I am the Chinese inspector of the British Concession Police Station,
Zhou Wei.
Inspector Zhou, what brings you to my police station?
Under the orders of Chief Inspector Zhu,
I am here
to extradite the suspect, a doctor at St. George's Hospital,
Richard Pitt,
back to the police station.
I'm sorry.
Pitt is suspected of a serious crime.
He is currently under our investigation,
so we cannot hand him over to you.
Inspector Jiang,
you know
he is protected by consular jurisdiction.
The Chinese side has no right to detain or interrogate him.
Inspector Zhou,
Pitt is a foreigner,
but the victims are our Chinese children.
I will definitely investigate this thoroughly.
I understand how you feel,
but I must execute this procedure.
Zhou Wei,
doing dirty work for foreigners,
aren't you afraid of divine retribution?
Look who it is.
It's our little foreign girl.
It seems your pretending to be a foreign mistress that day
was for the investigation.
As for interfering with the justice of the case,
I'll settle the score with you next time.
I'll be waiting for you to settle it.
Inspector Jiang,
I don't want to make things difficult for you,
so don't make things difficult for me.
I won't let him go.
You...
Let him go.
Mayor Zeng called.
This is his order.
Doesn't your stomach hurt?
Yes.
My stomach hurts.
It's been hurting all day.
If you hadn't come, I would have died of pain.
Take him to the hospital and keep a close watch on him.
Superintendent Li.
Did you know something happened to Peter?
He's been transferred to the Concession Police Station.
He's British.
So they can't convict him.
At a critical time like this,
you're the only one with a solution, Superintendent Li.
England.
Direct from Tanggu Pier to Liverpool.
When the time comes,
you can reunite with your son.
At my age,
I don't want to die in a foreign land.
How about this?
In a couple of years,
when things blow over,
I'll come back.
I'll definitely be able to make a comeback.
Then I'll continue to show my respect to you.
Alright.
Superintendent Li.
Wait,
didn't you say we were taking a boat?
Where is the pier?
Are you crazy?
If I drive a police car to take you to the pier,
wouldn't that let the whole world know
that I, Li Chengrui, let you escape?
Silly me.
Th-th-this is
for you to spend on the road.
Brother.
Words cannot express my gratitude.
Go through this forest.
Someone will meet you soon.
Go.
Posing?
Did I look handsome just now?
Handsome my ass.
Give it to me.
Ah my ass.
Take me to the hospital.
Okay, okay.
Hurry.
Mr. Wang,
why are you here?
Lei Lie is dead.
When did this happen?
Just last night.
I examined the body.
The bullet in Lei Lie
came from Yao Qiang's gun.
Where is Li Chengrui?
Li Chengrui said he went to the hospital.
Today's newspaper
reported the death of the Jiuhe Gang leader
and suppressed the news about Peter.
Peter is still at large,
but the higher-ups issued an official document
requiring our Phoenix Police Department
to take responsibility for Lei Lie assaulting the police and escaping.
Zheng Kun was silenced.
Bai Xianming is dead and can't testify.
Lei Lie was killed resisting arrest.
Peter was deported.
Is it the incompetence of the police,
or are these pieces of evidence useless?
And now they want us to take responsibility for this.
Inspector Jiang,
Where are you going?
We can't just let the matter with Peter go.
I'll go with you.
Are you comfortable?
What do you think the Chinese police
can do to me?
I can still have fun with Chinese women, can't I?